Elham Salmanian

Full stack development experience in ideation to product launch for a medical tech start-up, Experience in IT CRM (technical customer support) managing a team of support staff Experience in developing REST APIs, experience in jQuery, databases (MySQL), Experience with Git, PyCharm, IntelliJ IDEA, Self-starter, team player and multitasker, strong interpersonal communication, Experience working on an agile team and strong communication and collaboration skills, Experience in create app with Django (python framework), Ability to find best model for prediction of data (ML).

Work History

2021-02 to present

Full stack developer (react, Node.js) 2020-2021 Toronto

- Part of the initial full stack development team
- Participated in product ideation and beta product development
- Successfully launched the first version of the app
- Responsible for creating front end and back end for the clinical app
- User Interface and Experience design of the pages using react and Node.js

Reference: https://novel-one.vercel.app/

2012-2014

Technical Customer Support , Karmania, Iran

- Responsible for registering Host and Domain for customers
- Monitoring and maintaining an organization's computer systems and networks
- Responsible for diagnosing and solving application failures either in person or over the phone.
- Working with product management during discovery discussions and delivery plan
- Experienced in agile software development and participated in scrum meetings

Projects

- Bud Repair-Car App (2020)
- To make the car repair process digitized
- Backend: Python, frontend: Angular, DB: MongoDB | Database on CRUD app
- House price analyzer(2019)
- Used machine learning to analyze and predict house prices
- Python, R, NumPy/SciPy/Pandas
- KNN, Classifier, Support Vector Classifier, Decision Tree Classifier and Random Forest Classifier
- Chat Application(2020)
- Frontend: Angular, DB: MongoDB

Personal Info

Address

Canada, Toronto, 6 Avonmore Sa

Phone

4168581030

E-mail

elham.salmanian@gmail.com

Skills

Data Science

- Sci-kit Learn
- Predictive Modeling
- Keras
- Tensor Flow
- Deep Learning

Computer Programming

- JavaScript
- React
- Pandas
- Python
- C#
- git
- Node.is

Education

2014

2020 Bachelor's degree of Computer Programming Analyst ,George Brown College

Bachelor of Agriculture engineering, Bahonar university Graduate